[
  {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "An entity can only have one Primary UID. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 2,
    "question": "If an entity has no attribute suitable to be a Primary UID, we can create an artificial one. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 3,
    "question": "There is no limit to how many columns can make up an entity's UID. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 4,
    "question": "A unique identifier can only be made up of one attribute. True or False?",
    "correct": "False",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 5,
    "question": "When is an entity in 2nd Normal Form?",
    "correct": "When all non-UID attributes are dependent upon the entire UID.",
    "answers": [
      "When all non-UID attributes are dependent upon the entire UID.",
      "When attributes with repeating or multi-values are present.",
      "When no attritibutes are mutually independent and all are fully dependent on the primary key.",
      "None of the Above."
    ]
  },
  {
    "number": 6,
    "question": "An entity can only have one Primary UID. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 7,
    "question": "If an entity has no attribute suitable to be a Primary UID, we can create an artificial one. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 8,
    "question": "There is no limit to how many columns can make up an entity's UID. True or False?",
    "correct": "True",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 9,
    "question": "A unique identifier can only be made up of one attribute. True or False?",
    "correct": "False",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "number": 10,
    "question": "When is an entity in 2nd Normal Form?",
    "correct": "When all non-UID attributes are dependent upon the entire UID.",
    "answers": [
      "When all non-UID attributes are dependent upon the entire UID.",
      "When attributes with repeating or multi-values are present.",
      "When no attritibutes are mutually independent and all are fully dependent on the primary key.",
      "None of the Above."
    ]
  }
]
